computersourcebd.com 2016-06-25

# Computer Source | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Computer Source Limited. Being the leader in providing technology to the numerous users CSL feels the need to treat its customers according to a privacy policy that confirms how we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store your information. We appreciate your interest in Computer Source Limited and our products and services. We do our best to serve you and receive your trust. Please take a look at our privacy policies to build a strong relationship.

## Personal Information Collection and Usage

You may be asked to provide your personal information anytime you are in contact with Computer Source Limited.CSL and its partners in business, if necessary, may share this personal information with each other and use it to handle both regular and emergency situations. This information will be helpful for continuous product development, new market analysis and coverage, developing plans and executing strategies and providing quality services to you.

### What personal information we collect

  * When you purchase products from outlets at different places in Bangladesh, pay on your credit or debit card, contact us for service or query, participate in survey or promotional activities we may collect a variety of information  including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, contact preferences, and credit card information.
  * When you receive any kind of gifts or discounts from CSL on special occasion or promotional periodwe may collect the information such as name, mailing address, email address, and phone number of the personyou would like to take in with you to enjoy offers. 
  * We may also ask for your Voter ID Card Number to make the deal between you and CSL stronger and trustworthy.

### How we use your personal information

  * The personal information we collect allows us to keep contact with you to know your level of satisfaction after purchasing our products. It also helps us to cope up with your change in preference and level of comfort. According to this information we improve our services, content, and advertising. If you don’t want to be on our mailing list, you can opt out anytime by contacting us. 
  * We also use personal information for continuous R&D enabling us for quicker response to our clients. 
  * From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with CSL. 
  * As part of corporate culture CSL maintains strong rules and regulations for internal purposes such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve products, services and customer communications. Your personal information will help us in knowing customer demands and planning our schedules and programs according to that. 
  * Computer Source Limited is very much aware of its corporate social responsibilities. Our social efforts have been praised several times and we feel that without CSR it is not possible for a corporation to sustain in competition. To let people know our activities for social development and awareness we may share your personal data such as name, address on both electronic and print media provided that you have received special consideration from CSL for your attachment with society. 

## Collection and Use of Non-Personal Information

We also collect non-personal information − data in a form that does not permit direct association with any specific individual. We may collect, use, transfer and disclose non-personal information for any purpose. The following are some examples of non-personal information that we collect and how we may use it:

  * We may collect information such as occupation, language, zip code, area code and location where our products will be used so that we can better understand customer behavior and improve our products, services and advertising. 
  * We also may collect information regarding customer activities on our website through electronic (web based) form. This information is combined and used to help us provide more useful information to our customers and to understand which parts of our website, products and services are of most interest. 

If we do combine non-personal information with personal information the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.

## Disclosure to Third Parties

At times CSL may make certain personal information available to strategic partners that work with CSL to provide products and services. For example, when you purchase product with warranty the information you provide on invoices will be used in the warranty cards and in future this card will be available to our strategic partners at the time you claim your warranty.  Personal information will only be shared by CSL to provide or improve our products, services and advertising accomplished jointly with our partners; it will not be shared with third parties for their own marketing purposes.

### Service Providers

CSL shares personal information with companies who provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, assessing your interest in our products and services and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys. These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever Apple operates.

### Others

It may be necessary − by law, legal process and/or requests from public and governmental authorities for CSL to disclose your personal information. On the grounds of national security, law enforcement or other issues of public importance CSL will provide your personal information to respective authority.   
CSL may also disclose information about you if it becomes necessary for us to enforce our terms and conditions or protect our operations or users. For strategic business purposes and establishing strategic alliances CSL may share your personal information.

## Protection of Personal Information

CSL takes safeguards including administrative, technical and physical measures to protect your personal information against loss, theft and misuse as well as against unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

In future customers will be able to purchase and order products through our online services. They may also claim their service warranty. In that case we will combine our web page with latest security measures to protect your personal data. Our efficient and intelligent web developer team will always monitor your information.

CSL maintains several pages on different social networking sites. You may be one who will follow us. Here the personal information you share will be visible to other users and can be read, collected or used by them. You will be responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these instances.

## Integrity and Access to Personal Information

Computer Source Limited respects its customers and believes that they are the force behind the success. So, CSL is very much aware regarding the integrity of personal data of its customers. CSL promises customers that their valuable information will remain accurate and will not be modified for any purpose. Besides, our web developer team is determined to open the opportunity for the users to access their information and update them accordingly.

## Services at Distant Locations

CSL is committed to provide services from every corner of Bangladesh to the customers. Already we have our outlets at several towns and we are planning to reach all the district level towns and cities. Customers will be able to purchase all the available products from their nearby outlet. Due to our commitment for providing superior service we handle all kinds of warranty issues centrally. Customers may have to contact head office to get their full warranty support. We would like to say that this is required for confirmation of delivery and we encourage our clients to do this. We hope that the relationship between us will be enhanced. CSL assures that customers will receive assistance from our local outlets for the warranty issues.

## Age Verification

Computer Source Limited expects reasonable behavior from the customers and treats them like that. Sensitive issues such as claim on warranty, service, product handling, software installation, uninstallation and updating etc. are applicable only to the users who are adult enough to understand these issues. CSL discourages invoicing with person under 15 years old and is not interested keeping records of personal information. 

Computer Source Limited has been able to maintain a strong brand value in the ICT industry of Bangladesh through its commitment and integrity to the customers since 1994. CSL has never compromised with its quality and dedication to be the leader in the industry. Today, Computer Source Limited is considered the pioneer in bringing technology to the users and promises to carry on its responsibility in future. CSL hopes that its privacy policy will help customers to understand its commitment in business and bring themselves closer.

For any kind of query please contact:

**Computer Source Ltd.**  
House-11/B, Road-12 (New)  
Dhanmondi R/A, Dhaka-1209  
Tel: 9141747, 8125970, 8120578, 8128848, 9121484, 9140152  
Fax: +880-2-9118697  
Email: info@computersourcebd.com  
Web: [www.computersourcebd.com](http://www.computersourcebd.com/)
